Oh my darling, you took all that I am
The world outside is so inconceivable
You took me where I stand
Oh the morning, see the clouds,
They come in tow
The tide painted a tired seascape
Waiting for the blow
But I was never alone
I was never low
And so the feeling grows
The feeling grows
See the tide
See it shift to and fro
I’m all strung out searching
For answers that I will never know
So why were you a forest fire
Burning all that I had ever desired?
And why were you so quiet?
It was only in your silence
That I saw bone
But I was never alone
I was never low
And so the feeling grows
The feeling grows
You burnt me to the ground
I see that now
Looking back I see just how
Pain has made me better